- 吸血鬼后裔前情提要
Perviously on Legacies...
- 你不会还要我指出来
You don't want me to point out
你被马里之洼吞噬了吧
that you've been consumed by Malivore?
你又活了一天
That the big bad lived to see another day
然后有发现你所有的朋友都忘记了你的存在
and all your friends have forgotten you ever existed?
我根本不知道
I have absolutely no idea
之后要怎么办
what to do next.
你为什么不再用魔法了
Why have you stopped using your magic?
球场失误
Tenebris lapsus.
我伤害了别人
: I hurt someone.
我觉得是我想要这样
I think I wanted to.
我今年要追逐更大的目标
I'm hunting bigger game this year.
你喜欢的那个
That Sebastian dude
叫塞巴斯蒂安的啊
you're crushing on?
他完全不知道我是什么样的人
He doesn't know anything about me.
自从你走之后
Raf has been stuck in wolf form
拉夫就一直困在狼人模样回不来了
ever since you've been gone.
拉夫  我知道你不记得我了
Raf. Look, I-I know you don't remember me,
但我可以帮你的
but I can help you.
我以为你不见了呢
I thought you were gone.
那女孩是谁啊
Who was that girl?
陆奥省
日本  1308年
不  我们晚上再走  你个恶心的寄生虫
恶心的新鲜皮囊
我早晚会杀了你的
你想都别想
掉头吧
不然就面对我的愤怒吧  恶魔
嘿
Hey, man.
没事吧你
Are you okay?
喂  大哥
Whoa, buddy. Hey!
我在哪  谁碰了我
你别走  我必须要知道  谁碰了我
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第4集
霍普·马歇尔请来校长办公室
ALARIC : Hope Marshall to the principal's office.
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
你还要广播叫我啊  是不是有点过了啊
P.A. system? It's a little dramatic, don't you think?
过也不如兰登给我留的消息过分啊
Not as dramatic as the message Landon left me,
他说有急事要商讨
saying he had something urgent to discuss.
- 你有什么要说的吗  - 就是
Anything you want to share? Only that
我很确定  这次怪物是在追他了
I'm pretty sure the monsters are after him this time.
那你不觉得应该告诉我吗
And you didn't think that that's something I should know?
我更害怕
More like I was
告诉你之后你要说的事情
afraid of what you were gonna say after that.
霍普
Hope.
翻 译  岛岛
你得回去萨尔瓦多的学校
You need to go back to the Salvatore School.
就是这句话
That was it.
不是为了你自己
Not for your sake.
为了他们
For theirs.
或许兰登对你来说没那么重要
Maybe Landon isn't that important to you.
翻 译  兔兔秃了
但如果马里之洼想要他  我们就得更想要他
But if Malivore wants him, we need to want him more.
我会搞定的  远远的搞定
Look, I will take care of it, but from a distance.
翻 译  RossyGeng
我有什么不知道的  霍普
Okay, what am I missing here, Hope? Hmm?
你跟我说了实话  一切不也都没事吗
You told me the truth, and everything worked out fine.
翻 译  Carousel
也不是全部的实话
Not the whole truth.
我和兰登
Landon and I...
曾经相爱的
we were in love.
真爱
: Like, real love.
特效：小螺号
史诗般的爱  如果存在的话
Epic love, if that even exists.
真的存在的
I can assure you it does.
校 对   岛岛
现在他和乔西好了
Now he's with Josie,
他们不知道我们以前的关系
and they don't know what we were to each other.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
特 效   麦 斯
我就是害怕如果我说了
And I'm just afraid that if I tell them,
他们俩会恨死我的
she's gonna hate me forever or he's gonna hate me
或者我自己会恨死我自己的  因为我让所有人都痛不欲生
or I'm gonna hate myself because I made us all miserable.
所以我不能说
So I can't tell them.
还不能
Not yet.
- 抱歉打扰了  - 没事的
Sorry to interrupt. No, it's okay.
我正要走呢
I was just leaving.
动员会再见咯
I will see you at the pep rally.
到时候见
See you there.
希望你考虑一下转学的事情
I hope you consider the transfer.
我可以帮你推荐过去那边的
I can put in a good word for you at the Salvatore School.
其实吧
Actually,
你不能再出现在这里30米之内了
you're no longer allowed within a hundred feet of its grounds.
什么
What?
法庭聆讯通知及临时限制令
"Notice of Court Hearing and Temporary Restraining Order"?
我不舒服  抱歉
I'm not feeling well, sorry.
抱歉你不舒服啊
VARDEMUS: I'm sorry to hear you're unwell.
我不舒服你还不知道怎么回事吗
You shouldn't be surprised.
是你给了我黑魔法咒语  正因如此
You gave me that black magic spell, and because of it,
我把那孩子胳膊搞断了  我自己情况也不怎么好
I broke that kid's arm, and mine's not doing so hot either.
你父亲怎么说的
What did your father have to say about this?
我还没机会跟他说呢
I-I haven't had the chance to ask him yet.
可以理解
That's understandable.
他正忙着吵架呢
He was busy starting brawls.
这也是你的错啊
I'm pretty sure that was your fault, too.
我或许有办法可以帮你缓解疹子
I may have something that can help that rash of yours.
我受够你的帮助了
I've had enough of your help.
我施了咒语  我要面对结果
I cast that spell, and I'm gonna deal with the consequences.
但我以后再也不碰黑魔法了
But I'm never doing black magic again.
我建议你不要着急限制自己
I would urge you not to limit yourself.
黑魔法在我们的魔法中
Black magic has
也是有一席之地的
its place in our craft.
我父亲说的正相反
My dad always said the exact opposite.
当然了
Of course.
我真是不明白
I cannot think of a single reason
他为什么要限制你非凡的能力
why he would want to limit your exceptional abilities.
如果你想找我
If you ever have need to talk...
我的大门永远为你敞开
...my door is always open.
我是说文艺复兴时期  不是文艺复兴节
I said Renaissance era, not Renaissance festival.
我可不想在塞巴斯蒂安面前搞角色扮演
I can't look like a cosplayer in front of Sebastian.
我们可以把袖子弄一下啊
We could take in the sleeve like this.
别
Don't.
把衣服弄好就行
Just fix it.
我花了一整个夏天提升自己
I spent a lot of time bettering myself over the summer,
我需要你你们也达到我的水准
and I need you all to rise to my level.
快一点
Now.
怎么样啊
MG: How's it going?
一点也不好
Terrible.
我是挺好的  但其他人
I mean, I'm great, but everyone else,
就很不好啊
terrible.
除了你
Except for you.
你真的很努力
You really tried
在帮我追塞巴斯蒂安呢
to help me with Sebastian.
谢了啊
Thanks.
对啊  这事吧
Yeah, um, about that.
我知道你很喜欢他的
Actually, um, I know you're all in with this guy, uh,
但我觉得你其实
but I think it might be best for you to keep
可以先不要更改你脸书上面的情感状态啊
your relationship status on the DL for a while.
为什么啊
Why would I do that?
这一切都是新的
It's all so new.
我担心可能你会看到什么
I'm worried you might be seeing things.
透过玫红色的镜片啥的
Through rose-colored glasses, I mean.
MG  我现在处于人生中情绪最好的时期
MG, I am in the best emotional shape of my life.
我得及时享乐
I need to carpe the diem.
活在当下啊
Seize the lay.
而且啊  朋友要互相支持啊
Oh, wow. Besides, friends should
我开心
support each other. If I'm happy,
你也开心
you're happy.
别多想啊
Don't overthink it.
你确定我们要这样吗
RAFAEL: You sure we should be doing this?
如果萨尔茨满博士觉得他可以不接我电话
If Dr. Saltzman thinks he can ignore my calls
好像我们不在一个地方住一样
like we don't live in the same town,
他就要出问题了
he's got another think coming.
而且是怪兽问题  如果他们又回来追我了
Namely monsters, because if they're back and after me now,
那说明马里之洼干涸的那晚
I must've done something to screw up
我肯定搞砸了什么事情
the night the Malivore pit went dry.
而且如果我记不起来呢
And if I can't remember any of it,
我们就需要他帮忙搞清楚哪里出了问题
we need his help to figure out what changed
怎么解决  不然所有人就都有危险
and how to fix it, or we're all in danger.
你在听我讲话吗
Are you even listening to me?
嗯嗯  我一直都听呢
Yeah, I'm always listening.
那你还说话吗
Well, do you speak anymore?
自从你回了学校之后
I mean, ever since you got back to school,
你说话都没有超过三个字了
your sentences have averaged three words each.
才不是
That's not true.
你看  三个字
That's three words.
你怎么不看路啊
Hey, man, watch what you...
我知道你说你没事  但你被卡在狼人形状太久了
Look, I know you say you're fine, but you were stuck
是  但我现在恢复了啊
as a wolf for a pretty long time. Yeah, and I'm back now.
所以没事了
So it's all good.
多谢霍普啊
Thanks to Hope.
是啊  她一直都很厉害
Yeah, she was pretty incredible.
所以你还真是因为这个跟我来的
why you came with me.
- 什么   - 你只是想再见霍普吗
What? You just want to see Hope again?
不啊  我不想让这些怪物接近你啊
No. I, um, want to stop these monsters from getting to you.
如果见到了霍普  也不错啊
And if we see Hope, I mean, that's-that's cool, too.
确实不错啊
Yeah, it would be cool, too.
你没事吧
Hey, are you okay?
拉夫  拉夫
Raf? Raf? Raf?
慢点啊
MAN: Slow down!
大哥  我去找个能听懂日语的好吧
Dude, I'm gonna find someone who can
但你先别在这捅来捅去的了
understand you, but I need to know
你好啊
you're not gonna go stabbing... Konichiwa.
你啥时候会说日语了
Since when do you speak Japanese?
因为丽兹之前的心理治疗就在一个日语学校旁边啊
Since Lizzie's old therapist was next to a Japanese language school.
库鲁塔
...Kurutta.
他说什么
Uh... What's he saying?
他疯了吗
He's crazed?
库鲁塔
Kurutta.
这好像是他的名字啊
Oh, I think that's his name.
也是疯了的意思
Also, another word for "crazed."
他是恶魔猎人吗
He's a... demon hunter?
在找一个恶鬼
Looking for an Oni,
就是类似于恶魔鬼魂怪物的一个东西吧
which is like a demon- ghost-monster kind of a thing.
这应该就是下一个马里之洼怪物了
Sounds like that's our next Malivore monster.
那这个恶鬼估计跟兰登在一起呢
Then the Oni's probably wherever Landon is.
他说他跟随着他的来到这里
Uh, he said he followed his sword here,
然后会发光的
and it glows around...
在  什么玩意旁边
Jintsu-riki?
哦对  邪恶力量
Oh, oh, supernaturals.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
好吧  也说明他为啥跑到这来了
Okay. Makes sense why he wound up here.
但这玩意我还没见过呢
But I've never seen one of those.
他说我们不知道恶鬼到没到这里
He said that we wouldn't know if the Oni was here or not.
它会附身到人身上的
It possesses people,
可能在任何地方
and it could be anywhere.
任何人身上
In anyone.
看路啊 哥们
Watch yourself, bro.
祝你化学挂科
Go fail chemistry.
嘿
Hey.
我不该让你跟我一起来的  我们走吧
I shouldn't have asked you to come with me. We can go.
拉夫
Raf?
Raf.
拦住
Scalare.
霍普
Hope.
你怎么总能在对的时间出现在对的地方
How are you always in the right place at the right time?
有意思
That's funny.
我的想法正好相反
I was just thinking the exact opposite thing.
你在这  我正找你呢
There you are. I need you.
找我是要跟我道歉吗
So you can apologize for this?
你又使用黑魔法了吗
Are you seriously using black magic again?
我要提醒你  无论何时你做什么
Allow me to remind you that whenever you do,
发生在你身上的事也会发生在我身上
whatever happens to you happens to me, too.
我很抱歉
And I'm so sorry.
不会有下次了
It won't happen again.
你走运了
Well, you're just lucky
正好塞巴斯蒂安喜欢老式的造型
that Sebastian appreciates the old-fashioned look.
那是谁啊
Who the hell is that?
- 说来话长  - 长话短说
- Long story. - Short version?
他是一个找不到恶鬼的恶魔猎人
He is a samurai/demon hunter
我们杀死他的唯一方法是
who lost his Oni and the only way we can kill it
在他把兰登带到马里之洼之前
is with his demon-banishing sword
用驱魔剑杀了他
before it carries off Landon into Malivore.
你能帮我吗
Can you come?
我想如果我重新安排我的日程
Well, I suppose if I reschedule my date,
会给这皮疹一段时间让它痊愈
it would give this rash some time to clear up.
啊  谢谢你  谢谢  谢谢
Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you.
库鲁塔
Kurutta.
他在说我  是吗
He's talking about me, isn't he?
- 他说我疯了  - 不
- He's calling me crazy. - No.
不是  他说的是恶鬼
No, he's talking about the Oni.
它占有人类  使之疯狂
It possesses people, crazy.
那我收回我的提议
Well, then I retract my offer.
我的精神健康是我拥有的最宝贵的东西  乔
My mental health is the most precious thing that I have, Jo.
我能对付皮疹
A rash I can deal with,
但我不能冒险跟疯子一起去  我很抱歉
but I cannot risk crazy. I'm sorry.
谢谢你让我留下来
Thanks for letting me stay.
上次我问玛雅她过得怎么样
Last time I asked Maya what was going on in her life,
她说我多管闲事
she called me a narc.
我想这意味着你做的是对的
Well, I guess that means you're doing something right.
我们在这里
Here we are...
关于禁令
About that restraining order--
我只是在做我的工作
I was just doing my job.
但私下里  我能实话实说吗
But off the record, can I be honest?
我倒希望大家都坦诚相待呢
I wish more people would be.
那个校长是个混蛋
That headmaster is a dick.
我很抱歉  等我一下好吗
I'm sorry. Will you give me a moment?
加油  狼人队
Let's go, Wolves!
你们俩来这干什么
What were you two even doing here?
寻找答案
Looking for answers.
我猜  就是你吧
And, I guess... you.
- 爸爸  - 乔西
- Dad? - Josie.
到底怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
他说  我们是来保护那个
He said, "We came to protect
爆炸头男孩的
the bonsai-headed boy."
我觉得
I think.
这是日语的
That's Japanese for,
她到底在这儿干什么
"What the hell is she doing here?"
我一开始
This is not
可没想掺和这个啊
what I signed up for.
抱歉  老兄
Sorry, brotato.
视频俱乐部成员优先获得设备
AV club members get equipment priority.
你是视频俱乐部里唯一的成员  维斯
You're the only one in the AV club, Wes.
- 我叫韦德  - 无所谓
- It's Wade. - Whatever.
听着  我要帮朋友做个项目
Look, I need to help a friend with a project.
很重要的事  这可能是我唯一能让她
An important one. This might be the only way
看到真相的方法
I could get her to see the truth.
真实的电影
Cinema verité.
我觉得不错啊
I can dig it.
这段时间在镜头前很难熬
All this time travel's been hard on the camera, Bon.
在这里
There it is.
耶
Yay!
- 这是用过的带子  - 谁在乎呢
- This tape is used. - Who cares?
就覆盖掉就好了啊
Just record over it.
仅仅因为她有超能力并不意味着我们可以信任她
Just because she's supernatural doesn't mean we can trust her.
我是说  她不应该在这里的
I mean, she shouldn't be here.
听着  我会接受所有的帮助
Look, I will take all the help I can get.
甚至是他的帮忙
Even from him.
所以请他告诉我们应该知道的一切
So ask him to tell us everything we should know.
库鲁塔君
Kurutta-san.
在他还是婴儿的时候  磕到头了
Dropped on his head as a baby.
到武士学校学习纪律
Samurai school to learn discipline.
恶鬼
Oni--
恶魔   这是我们一直追逐的
demons, which is what we're chasing.
他是个英雄
He was a hero.
所有的女人都恳求
All the women begged to...
库鲁塔君  我都不知道这个词
Kurutta-san, I don't even know that word,
但你别瞎说啊
but it cannot be relevant.
乔西  说重点
Josie, the point.
回到点子上
Let's get to it.
库鲁塔花了几个月的时间追踪一个附身于人的恶鬼
Kurutta spent months tracking down an Oni
通过触摸从一个人移动到另一个人
that possessed people, moving from person to person by touch.
他刚要杀它
He was just about to kill it
它就钻进了一个孩子的身体里
when it found its way into the body of a child
又一次逃脱了
and escaped him yet again.
他追赶并抓住了恶魔
He gave chase and caught the demon.
但是他不能伤害一个无辜的孩子
But he could not bring himself to harm an innocent child.
所以  他做出了一个不可能的选择
So, instead, he made an impossible choice
他让恶鬼附在自己身上
and he took the Oni into himself.
但就在那时  他意识到
But it was then that he realized, unlike everyone else
不像其他人那样被附身之后  什么都不记得
who had been possessed and remembered nothing,
他仍然能在一定程度上控制着自己的能力
he was still partly in control of his faculties.
他认为恶鬼发现很难控制
He thinks the Oni found it harder
他破碎的思想
to possess his broken mind.
我只是复述啊
His words, not mine.
他试图用剑刺自己
He tried to stab himself with his sword,
恶鬼不让他这么做
and the Oni wouldn't let him.
所以他决定
So he decided to
永远不再碰别人
never touch a person again--
这样恶鬼就永远不能附身别人
So that it could never possess anyone else.
然后
And then...
马里之洼  永恒的虚无
Malivore, eternity of nothingness...
受深深的心理折磨
...deep psychological torment.
他经历了
He came through an...
我想他说的是传送门
I think he's talking about a portal.
- 传送门  在哪里  - 抱歉
- Portal? Uh, where? - sorry,
这位古代武士并不是
the ancient samurai isn't an expert
神秘瀑布镇的地理专家
on Mystic Falls geography.
我们怎么杀死恶魔
How do we kill the... the demon?
用他的剑
Uh, with his sword.
它被施了一种特殊的魔法
It's spelled with a special kind of magic,
如果我们能找到恶鬼
so if we can just find the Oni...
找到了啊
Not a problem.
等等  不  不  不  不
Wait, no, no, no, no!
瞬移
Motus.
他说本来可以做得更好的
He said that could've gone better.
该死  我想知道拉夫是否接触了其他人
Damn. I wonder if Raf already touched someone.
是啊  只要找那些行为古怪的人就行了
Yeah, just look for anyone acting strange or erratic.
森林狼队  森林狼队  森林狼队
Timberwolves! Timberwolves! Timberwolves!
森林狼队
Timberwolves!
你是说除了橄榄球队之外的人吗
You mean besides the football team?
有个学生需要你的帮助
There's a student that needs your help.
拉夫
Raf?
霍普  等等
Hope, wait.
不要碰他
Don't touch him.
拉夫
Raf?
嘿
Hey.
哦  是你  对吧
Oh, yeah, that's you, isn't it?
是
Yeah.
我控制不住我自己了
I wasn't in control back there.
没关系  我可以帮你
It's okay. I-I can help you.
我只是想知道
I-I just need to know
你有没有碰过别人
if there's anyone that you've touched
或者谁碰过你
or who might've touched you.
- 我什么都不记得了  - 好吧
- I don't remember any of it. - Okay.
整合
Inteo.
这是障碍咒
Barrier spell.
意思是没有我的允许
Means that no one can get in or out
任何人都不能进出
without me saying so.
包括你
Including you.
这是因为霍普吗
Is this about Hope?
看来她不是今天唯一一个
Guess she's not the only one
能救你的人
that gets to save your life today.
- 所以不用谢  - 乔西  你知道
- So you're welcome. - Josie, you know
我是个死而复生的人  对吧  我不是一个坐以待毙的人
I'm a phoenix, right? I'm not a sitting duck.
- 我们还有其他选择  - 好吧
- We have other options here. - Okay.
说一个吧
Name one.
马里之洼给我送来了恶鬼
Malivore sent the Oni for me.
所以我说不如让恶魔附在我身上
So I say we let the demon possess me,
然后你用这把剑杀了我
and then you kill me with this sword.
恶魔被征服  我复活  我们胜利了
Demon gets vanquished, I resurrect, we win.
不管有用没用  兰登
If it works, Landon.
我也不会把你交给恶魔来证明的
I'm not handing you to some demon to find out.
这正是我想跟你爸爸说的
This is exactly what I wanted to talk to your dad about.
强迫每个人都把自己置于危险之中
Forcing everyone else to put themselves in danger
来阻止下一个袭击我的怪物
to stop whatever monster's coming after me next
是一种不可持续的解决方案
is an unsustainable solution.
不  垃圾填埋场是一个不可持续的解决方案
No, landfills are an unsustainable solution.
但让你活着不是  结束讨论
Keeping you alive is not. End of discussion.
怎么了
What is it? What's wrong?
它被施了黑魔法
It's spelled with black magic.
有很多咒语
A lot of it.
这是我们不这样做的另一个原因
Another reason we are not doing this.
等等  你要去哪里
W-Wait, where are you going?
找人帮忙
To get backup.
我打赌如果我被附身了  你会捅我
I bet you'd stab me if I was possessed.
- 你们找到拉夫了吗  - 是的
- Did you find Raf? - Yeah.
我们把他送回了学校   他身上没有恶鬼
We sent him back to campus. The Oni wasn't in him,
- 所以它可能在其他地方  - 我会找到它
- so it could be anywhere. - I'll find it.
只要你说服兰登不要牺牲自己
As long as you convince Landon not to sacrifice himself
- 来阻止这件事  - 不
- to stop this thing. - No.
不  他不能那么做
Uh, no, he-he can't do that.
我是说  我们不能给恶魔它想要的
I mean, we can't give the monster what it wants.
尤其是当它想要的是我男朋友的时候
Especially when what it wants is my boyfriend.
他这么做是因为
Who's only doing this because
他认为这都是他的错
he thinks that it's all his fault.
你男朋友吗
Boyfriend?
我可以试着劝劝他
Why don't I try to talk some sense into him.
好吧
Okay?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我很享受我们在一起的时光
I have so enjoyed our time together.
我也一样
Same.
虽然我觉得我们之间还不够亲密
Though I feel that we are not as close as we could be.
我还是希望我们能
And I wish for us to be...
肌肤相亲
...skin to skin.
我只有一个问题想问
I have but one question to ask.
嗯
: Yeah.
- 你有途径为我提供  - 不  我不是处女
Do you have access to... No, I am not a virgin.
中到大量的人类血液供应吗
...a moderate-to-large supply of human blood?
我知道这看起来很不好
I know how this looks.
比如你是个变态的跟踪狂吗
Like you're a freaking stalker?
快滚吧  趁塞巴斯蒂安
Leave now, before Sebastian
- 还没揍扁你  - 丽兹
kicks your ass. Lizzie.
我认为问题不在这里
I don't think that's gonna be a problem.
好吧  我会锤爆你的
Fine I am gonna kick your ass.
听着  把这东西从我面前拿开
Look, just... Get this thing out of my face.
只是看一下  拜托了
Just watch it. Please.
不  我不是处女
No, I'm not a virgin.
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
塞巴斯蒂安刚才就在我旁边
Sebastian was right next to me.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
但这是我能想到的唯一能让你
But this was the only way I could think of
看到其他人所看到东西的方法
to get you to see what everyone else is gonna see.
赛巴斯蒂安并不是真实存在的
Sebastian's not real.
别说了
Shut up.
Just shut up.
你和我
You and me...
我们根本不是朋友
we're not friends.
我们过去不是  将来也不会是
We never were, and we never will be.
看清楚吧
So see this:
我对你毫不在意
you don't exist to me.
嘿
Hey.
乔西解除了障碍咒  所以我就能进来了
Josie dropped the barrier spell so I could get in.
有个恶魔在学校里的某个地方游荡
There's a demon loose inside the school somewhere.
我们得把你送到安全的地方
We have to get you to somewhere safe.
- 没有地方是安全的  - 好吧  好吧
There is nowhere safe. Okay, well,
找个比这里安全的地方
somewhere safer than here.
如果这是唯一能杀死
If this is the one thing
恶鬼的东西  那这可能也是唯一能杀死
that can kill an Oni, what if it's the one thing
凤凰的东西呢
that can kill a phoenix, too?
乔西告诉我
Josie told me that
你认为怪物回来了是你的错
you think the monsters being back is your fault.
但事实并非如此
But it isn't.
你知道些什么吗
What do you know about it?
很多
Too much.
相信我  兰登
Trust me, Landon, even though
即使你的出发点是好的
you might have the best intentions,
但不是所有的牺牲都是值得的
not every sacrifice is worth it.
不管你认为这有多重要
No matter how much you think it is.
你说这不是我的错
You said this isn't my fault?
确实不是
It isn't.
那是谁的错
Then whose is it?
这并不重要  我们需要
That doesn't matter. We need to...
这对我很重要
It matters to me.
这是我的错
It's my fault.
我是那个陷入麻烦的人
I'm the one that went into the pit.
我以为这是唯一能救你的办法
I thought it was the only way to save you.
你为什么要救我
Why would you want to save me?
因为我们曾经是  我们曾是朋友
Because we were... we were friends.
拜托  一定有比这更深的原因
Come on, there had to be more to it than that.
告诉我
Tell me.
如果我说了  你会恨我的
You're gonna hate me if I do.
让我自己做决定
Let me make that decision for myself.
我们曾经相爱过
We were in love.
我知道你不记得了
Yeah, I know that you don't remember.
我知道这听上去很荒谬
I know that it doesn't make any sense.
但我不能让你
But I can't let you
冒生命危险  因为我曾试图放弃生命来挽回一切
risk your life because I tried to give up mine to save it.
所以  我们必须找到另一个解决方案
So, uh, we have to find another solution.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
一个不会让你被附身的
One that doesn't involve you being possessed.
太迟了
It's too late.
发生了什么   兰登在哪儿
What happened? Where's Landon?
乔西  给她点时间
Josie, just give her a second.
但你说过你会帮忙的
But you said you were gonna help.
- 你被附身了吗  - 没有
Were you possessed? No.
- 是兰登  - 这不可能
Landon was. That's impossible.
怎么会
How?
我们以为拉夫会在
Uh, we thought Raf was gonna
赛前动员会上把恶鬼交给某人看管
pass the Oni on to somebody at the pep rally.
库鲁塔一定是在拉夫袭击他之后被附身的
Kurutta must've been possessed after Raf attacked him.
恶鬼等待单独和兰登在一起时机
The Oni waited to be alone with Landon,
然后控制了他
took control of him and...
永别了  武士
Sayonara, samurai.
好吧  那他会去哪儿
Okay, well, where would he have gone?
我猜是传送门
I mean, my guess is the portal.
我们甚至不知道它在哪里
Well, we don't even know where that is.
等等  你有兰登的东西吗
Wait. Do you have something of Landon's?
因为你们俩现在都可以做定位咒了
'Cause you both could do a locator spell right now.
是的  但那不是我的
Yeah, but that's not mine.
警长一定是拉下了这个
ALARIC: The sheriff must have left this.
情书吗
Love note?
那不是给你的
That's not for you.
笨蛋  笨蛋  笨蛋
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
他当然不是真的
Of course he isn't real.
没人真正喜欢你
No real guy ever likes you,
因为你的内心一团糟
'cause you're messed up inside.
每个人都知道
And everybody knows it.
除了你
Everyone except you.
因为你是个喜欢自言自语的又蠢又疯狂的家伙
Because you are a stupid, crazy person who talks to herself.
你为什么带着把剑
: Why are you carrying a sword?
兰登
Landon!
拿来
Fugere.
我猜你被一个疯狂的恶魔附身了
I'm guessing you're possessed by an insanity demon.
欢迎入伙
Welcome to the club.
这是带妆彩排
Dress rehearsal.
欢迎大家来观看我们
Please come to our full
在英联邦日的历史重制表演
historical reenactment performance on Commonwealth Day.
我还以为我疯了
MAC: Oh. I thought I was losing my mind.
谢谢你找到我的包
Thanks for finding my... bag.
我以真诚待你
I was honest with you.
你至少得跟我说实话
The least you can do is be honest with me.
这是个天大的误会
This is a huge misunderstanding.
那你为什么不放下伪装
Then why don't you drop the act?
不管你想要什么  你跟我说
Whatever you want, you talk to me.
别把我女儿扯进来
And you leave my girls out of this,
不然我们就麻烦大了
or we're gonna have a problem.
我只是看了你的档案
I only looked at your files
因为我想看看你是不是个好人
because I wanted to see if you were a good guy.
然后我调查了你的女儿
And then I looked into your girls
因为我想知道你是不是个好爸爸
'cause I wanted to see if you were a good dad.
我为我想约你出去感到抱歉
So, sorry for wanting to ask you out.
不会再发生这种事了
It won't happen again.
兰登
Landon!
丽兹  你没事吧
Lizzie, are you okay?
不
No.
我彻底疯了
I am super crazy.
但至少这次是有原因的
But at least there's a reason this time.
有个恶魔在我体内
The demon's in me.
- 所以你以为我是个疯子吗  - 没错
So you thought I was a lunatic? Oh, yeah.
顺便说一句  现在还没有定论
I mean, jury's still out, by the way.
我很抱歉  我很难信任别人
I'm sorry. I've got trust issues.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
在感情方面  我有
I have a long history of bad luck
很长一段倒霉史
when it comes to relationships.
把那件事推给你是不公平的
It's not fair to put that on you.
我这什么破侦探啊  是吧
Some detective, huh?
没关系  我也有一段很长的经历
That's okay. I've got one of those long histories, too.
我知道
Oh, I know.
看过了你的档案  还记得吗
Read your file. Remember?
然而  我却在这里  和你打情骂俏的
And yet, here I am, flirting with you.
这难道不就是我们要做的吗
Is that what we're doing? Mm-hmm.
真的搞砸了  不是吗
Really screwed this up, didn't we?
至少我们都为此努力过
Well, at least it was a team effort.
告诉你吧
Uh, tell you what.
我今晚会去神秘瀑布酒吧
I'll be at the Mystic Tap later tonight,
如果你想喝一杯的话
if you want to get a drink.
重新开始
And a clean slate.
抱歉  真是不好意思呢
Oh, sorry, that is embarrassing.
我们还没见过面  是吗
We haven't met yet, have we?
我是丽兹
I'm Lizzie.
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果恶鬼在你体内  那你怎么能说话
If the Oni is in you, then how are you talking?
我不知道  但我能感觉到它我的脑海里
I don't know, but I-I can feel it in my head,
想接管我的身体
trying to take over.
我不知道我还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer I...
没事了
Never mind.
它走了
It's gone.
你可以松开我了
You can untie me.
这不是我说的
I didn't say that.
它说的  好吧
It did, okay?
还在我体内
Still in me, so don't--
听我说
Listen to me.
我没事
I'm fine.
我们应该离开这里趁还没
We should probably get out of here before we...
好吧  你们一定要阻止我
Okay. You have got to stop me.
拜托了  否则这个怪物就得逞了
Please. Otherwise, this thing is gonna win.
她在和恶魔作斗争  就像库鲁塔一样
She's fighting the demon somehow, like Kurutta did.
我已经知道自己疯了  你没必要反复讲
I already know I'm crazy, okay? You don't have to rub it in.
库鲁塔没疯  你也没疯
Kurutta was not crazy and neither are you.
爸爸呢  我要找爸爸
Where's Dad? I just want Dad.
库鲁塔和恶鬼打了很多年了
Kurutta fought the Oni for years, okay?
如果你能给我们点时间  那我们就能
If you can just give us a little bit of time, then we can...
不  我不想在这样活了
No. I can't live like this anymore.
塞巴斯蒂安不是真的
Sebastian isn't real.
一直以来  我都以为我好了
This whole time, I thought I was better,
但我一直能看见别人看不见的东西
but I have just been seeing things,
听到感觉到别人感觉不到的事情
and hearing things and feeling things that no one else does.
好吓人
And it's scary.
比我脑袋里的魔鬼还可怕
Scarier than any demon in my head.
尽管魔鬼也很可怕
Although that sucks, too.
丽兹
Lizzie.
丽兹  没事的
Lizzie, it's okay, okay?
我们会治好你的
We're gonna fix you. No.
我是治不好的  乔
There's no fixing me, Jo.
我已经支离破碎了
I am just... shattered.
碎得无法拼凑了
The pieces are too small to put back together.
告诉爸爸我爱他
Tell Dad that I love him.
但你得终结这一切
But you have to end this.
什么
What?
用这把剑
With that sword.
我知道我们才刚认识
Whoa. I know that we just met,
但我们不可能让你没命的
but there's no way that we are gonna let that happen.
你们别无选择
You have no choice.
不把那个男孩交出来这事就没完
This will not stop until you give me the boy.
丽兹
Lizzie?
丽兹  你要和这个魔鬼对抗
Lizzie, you got to fight this thing.
对抗也没用
Fighting is useless.
马里之洼还活着
Malivore still lives,
他对我们的掌控比以前更强大
and his control over us is stronger than ever.
不久  我们这些鬼怪就不关你们的事了
Soon, the likes of me will be the least of your concerns.
独白的时候分心了
Distracted during a monologue.
经典的混蛋错误
Classic villain mistake.
乔  你一定要这么做
Jo, you got to do this.
为了我
For me.
好吗
Okay?
反正你在合并前痛扁我
It's only a matter of time
只是时间问题
before you kick my ass in the Merge, anyway.
这可比合并要好  因为这一次
And this is better than the Merge, because this way
你脑子里再也不用和这样混乱的我
you won't have to live with some messed-up part of me
让你抓狂的我
in your brain forever,
一起生活了
driving you as crazy I am.
等我们找到解决办法再说这个
We weren't gonna talk about that until we had real solutions.
也许就是这个办法
Well, maybe this is it.
乔西  它又来了  求你了
Josie, it's coming back. Please.
你一定要动手
You got to do it.
如果乔西下不了手  就你来
If Josie won't do this, then you have to.
里面有大量黑魔法  握住会刺痛
There's so much black magic in it, it hurts to hold.
被刺可能也不好受
Probably won't feel much better getting stabbed by it.
我可以把里面的魔法逼出来
I can pull the magic out of this,
我也许可以把魔鬼从你身体里赶出来
I may be able to get the Oni out of you.
你做到了
You did it.
我爱你
I love you.
你好多了
You better.
嘿
Hey.
- 是你  - 把你送到这的人吗  是我
- It was you. - Uh, yeah, that moved you here? Yeah.
并不想让你在镇中心广场上冲进火焰
Didn't really want you bursting into flames in the middle of town square.
我说的不是这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
为何我每次死去都能看到你
Why do I see you every time I die?
你该回去找乔西了
You should get back to Josie.
萨尔茨曼小姐
Ms. Saltzman.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我施了黑魔法
I did black magic.
这次不是故意的
Not on purpose this time.
今早的公告之后
After this morning's declaration,
我只能认为这是出于必要
I can only assume it was absolutely necessary.
我真的很难受
I feel really sick.
你说你有东西能帮我
You said you had something that could help.
病痛调节仪
mora miserium,
是个给某些宗派的女巫使用的工具
a tool used by certain sects of witches
能抑制使用黑魔法后的病态
to withhold the ill effects of using such magic.
需要多久
For how long?
不确定
Indefinitely.
只要它不再粉碎了
So long as it doesn't shatter.
只需把手放在上面
Simply place your hands on the glass,
一切就生效了
and all will be as it should be.
我感觉好多了
I feel better.
见效了
I think it's working.
是的
Yes.
的确
It is.
你的相机还你
Here's your stupid camera back.
计划完成了吗
Done with your project already?
用不上了
No longer associated.
创造性有所不同
Creative differences.
抱歉  没看到你
Sorry. Didn't see you.
你对伊丽莎白说什么了
What did you say to Elizabeth?
我现在都接触不到她了
I am now no longer able to reach her.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian?
- 但你不能  - 喂
- But you can't... - Yo.
你跟谁说话呢
Who you talking to, man?
对了  他看不见我的
Oh, yes. No, he can't see me.
你并不是真实存在的
You're not even real.
不  我非常真实
No, I'm very real.
而且我需要你的帮助
And I need your help.
有人跟我说
* Someone told me *
写下清晰的事实
* Write clear and true *
写下伤痕
* About what hurts... *
我今晚就该在场的
I should have been there tonight.
陪着你和孩子们的
With you and the girls.
我尽顾着无关紧要的事去了
I got distracted from what matters most.
谢谢你
Thank you.
如果你不在的话
I don't know what would have happened
我不知道丽兹和乔西会出什么事
to Lizzie or Josie if you hadn't have been there.
她们比你想的更坚强
They're stronger than you think.
她们没用我帮忙
They didn't need my help.
也许吧
Maybe.
兰登呢
And what about Landon?
再说最后一遍  我不会回去的
For the last time, I'm not going back.
霍普  你告诉我的
Hope, you told me
你和兰登的爱情荡气回肠
that you and Landon shared an epic love.
未现的灰尘里
* In the ashes that unearth *
你在顾虑什么呢
So what's really holding you back?
有人跟我说
* Someone told me... *
如果我把一切都告诉他
I mean, what if I tell him everything,
他还想和乔西在一起怎么办呢
and he still wants to be with Josie?
我不知道
I don't know.
爱情没有界限
* Love has no limits... *
但你真的想不去找寻答案
But are you really gonna live the rest of your life
就这样过一辈子吗
without finding out?
没有界限
* No limits... *
我找的是是通往马里之洼的传送门
What I found was the portal to Malivore.
我要做的就是完成我做的事
And what I'm gonna do is finish what I started at the pit.
但这一次  我要完成好
But this time, I'm gonna get it right.
比言语更真
* With more than words. *
真好听
It's beautiful.
你回来我都没找到你  你还好吗
Couldn't find you when you got back. Are you okay?
我很好  我担心丽兹
I'm good. I'm worried about Lizzie.
我好像用够多的黑魔法伤了她
I kind of blasted her with enough black magic
把魔鬼从她脑子里面驱赶出来
to exorcise an army out of her head.
等等  你用了黑魔法
Wait. You did black magic?
是为了做好事
For the powers of good.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了
What?
你今天救了我
You saved my life today.
准确来讲  是丽兹救的
Well, technically, Lizzie did.
但我完全协助了  所以
But I totally got the assist, so...
无论怎样
Either way,
都超性感的
it's super sexy.
的确
It is.
让我们的世界充满生机
* Paint our own room full of life *
汽车行驶在夕阳之下
* Ride off in the sunset *
沉醉在此刻
* Get lost in the moment *
即使快乐转瞬即逝
* Even if it's just tonight *
宝贝  躺在床上
* Baby, sink in this bed *
我们一起凝视屋顶
* Stare with me at the ceiling *
我们躺在这里
* Let's lay here... *
还不行
Not yet.
就算幻想泯灭
* And if we slip away... *
但很快了
But soon.
我们也不会遗憾
* I promise we won't have regrets *
只求你让我爱你一生
* If you just let me love you to death *
虽然我不喜欢热闹
* Just 'cause I ain't one for crowds *
但你依然让我觉得骄傲
* Don't mean you don't make me proud *
我是无法逃避的人
* And I'm a hard pill to take *
不用找了
Keep the change.
我是首先开口的人
* And I'm the first one to say... *
我们没有等十年后
We did not wait ten years
才成为你的朋友  霍普·迈克尔森
to become friends with you... ...Hope Mikaelson.
霍普
Hope...
安德里亚  迈克尔森
Andrea... Mikaelson.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）